sevenreflections.com 2019-07-08

# Seven Reflections Privacy Policy

### Privacy Notice

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for SevenReflections.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this web site. 

### Information Collection, Use, and Sharing 

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone. 

We will use your information to respond to you or take an orders. We also may collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us, such as your name, address, phone number or email address. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order. 

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy. 

We use technologies like cookies (small files stored by your browser), web beacons, or unique device identifiers to anonymously identify your computer or device so we can deliver a better experience. Our systems also log information like your browser, operating system and IP address. 

We do not knowingly contact or collect personal information from children under 13. If you believe we have inadvertently collected such information, please contact us so we can promptly obtain parental consent or remove the information. 

To customize our service for you, we may collect and store your precise geographic location as part of your user profile. This data generally is not shared with others. 

We generally do not share personally identifiable information (such as name, address, email or phone) with other companies for marketing purposes. 

### Your Access to and Control Over Information 

You can sign into your account to see or delete any personally identifiable information we have stored, such as your name, address, email or phone number. You can also contact us by email to request to see or delete this information. 

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website: 

  * See what data we have about you, if any. 
  * Change/correct any data we have about you. 
  * Have us delete any data we have about you. 
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data. 

We have an [Opt Out](https://www.sevenreflections.com/account/?action=optout) option if you'd like to permanently remove your account. We don't share your information with third parties. 

### Ad Tracking

We do not allow advertising companies to collect data through our service for ad targeting. 

### Security 

We take reasonable administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to safeguard and protect your information from unauthorized access or disclosure. This includes utilizing Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts the personal information you input, and storing your information in encrypted form behind a firewall designed to block access from outside our network. However, no security or encryption method can be guaranteed to protect information from hackers or human error. 

Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business. 

### Contact

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please contact us: 

To operate the service, we also may make identifiable and anonymous information available to third parties in these limited circumstances: (1) with your express consent, (2) when we have a good faith belief it is required by law, (3) when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect our rights or property, or (4) to any successor or purchaser in a merger, acquisition, liquidation, dissolution or sale of assets. Your consent will not be required for disclosure in these cases, but we will attempt to notify you, to the extent permitted by law to do so. 

This privacy policy was last updated on June 3, 2017. Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on our website or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, push notification or text.
